you put a post on Facebook or put in a
Google request without it being started
a computer somewhere what is the cause
of each and every one of these problems
not to mention the deforestation the
environmental destruction Donald Trump
breath whatever what is the cause of
every single one of these problems now
you know so Satan anyone agree with that
what is the cause of every single one of
these problems because I tell you what
until we figure out what the actual
problem in there is no point shouting
about these things until we actually
identify the true cause of the problem
until we actually thought start to offer
some alternative list of solutions there
is little point about just shouting
about the problems so what is at the
root of all of these things what is the
single thing that lies at the heart of
all of these problems it is deeper than
that it's deeper either than that I mean
the system is a bit of a very term right
but the system is a bit of a tug it
always almost come not to mean anything
it's just an angry shell right but we
need we need to be better organized we
need to be more intelligent we need to
have better argument rather than
shouting that things are shit we have
got to be more constructive than there
so what lies at the heart of all of
these problems for me for me the
physical manifestation is money when
it's deeper than that we've been taught
we've come to believe we believe it deep
down in our souls that we are separate
from each other and that we didn't put
on this earth to compete with each other
this is not right we have heard of
without our sense of community our sense
of oneness of sense of
interconnectedness we've had that taken
away frozen until we claim that back
nothing is going to change the real
cause of all of the problems that I
mentioned is us we go along with this
shit
we don't shout loud enough we don't
object we don't fail to participate we
don't take personal risks this is what
we need to do actually want change these
are the things that you need to do just
standing and shouting that things that
shit
and yeah they shit I understand your
anger we all feel it but you've got to
express it in a constructive manner
within us anyway right my voice is about
to dive someone else wants to take the
megaphone I don't make any different
which one of these clouds into number
ten territory it makes no difference
nothing is going to change while we
continue to vote for these people
nobody's talking about the dissolution
of the monetary system nobody's talking
about actual democracy nobody's talking
about the evolution of evolution of the
first-past-the-post system nobody's
talking about multi-party politics you
know where are the real alternatives
when we go to vote there are none so
stop proposing in it if you want things
to change stop participating it that
which you know is evil and twist it and
wrong every time you go and vote every
time you take out alone you'll be
climbing into a credit card you are
legitimizing these things you wanna do -
magazine passes stop doing it
stop going along with it that is why I
continue because we go along with it how
many other thing is $200 it's pathetic
it's pathetic next year every single one
of you gets they make a plate but each
one of you free so people with use of
its being next year make a personal
question yourself right now get out
there we need to get out on the street
have more people doing this kind of
thing maybe one day someone from the
news agency will come down here and this
shit will get on TV right that is what
we need we need a platform on we take
and communicate but while we're throwing
beers of cars walking down the street
and share some the beautiful ink offices
and at each other we are going to get
fucking nowhere we look like a bunch of
bug or a boozer